FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I have 8 years of experience as a computer mechanic with a year of coding experience in JavaScript, Typescript, Python and Ruby. I am knowledgeable in both hardware and software, with a strong troubleshooting and communicating skill sets. I am a quick learner with passion for technology who is able to adapt in new environments.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Typescript, Ruby, Python, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: React.js, Express, Node.js, JQuery, Rails **Libraries**: Material UI, Bootstrap, Redux, React Router

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebase, GraphQL

EXPERIENCE

Store ManagerFeb 2017 – Feb 2022Uniway Computer Solutions LTDSaskatoon, Saskatchewan

• Provided affordable laptops during Covid pandemic for kids doing online courses.

• High customer satisfaction rating with an average of 4.7 stars on Google Review.

 Led a team of 4 technicians to provide technical support for individuals, businesses and government organizations.

Computer Mechanic

Uniway Computer Solutions LTD

Aug 2014 – Feb 2017 Saskatoon, Saskatchewan

- Troubleshooted hardware (e.g., replaced worn-out components with micro-soldering) and software (e.g., data recovery, remote control)
- Managed a computer repair shop as a senior computer mechanic, responsible for overseeing a team of 4 technicians and ensuring that all repairs were completed accurately and efficiently.

EDUCATION

LightHouse LabsDiploma in Full Stack Web Development

Online, Canada Jan 2023 – Apr 2023

University of Saskatchewan *BMSC in Microbiology and Immunology*

Saskatoon, Saskatchewan Sep 2010 – Aug 2014

PROJECTS

E-Clothing | React. is, Redux, Typescript, Firebase, StripAPI, Git | Source Code

July 2022 - Aug 2022

- Designed and developed a responsive e-commerce website with a user-friendly interface using HTML, CSS, and ReactJS and JavaScript
- Managing back end, authentication login and database with Firebase
- Built streamlined checkout process with **Stripe API**.

Natours | *Node.js, Express, JavaScript, Mapbox, Git* | <u>Source Code</u>

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed a responsive single page App with ReactJS. Users could leave commits and ratings, with a secure authentication cookie sending JSON Web Token.
- A CRUD application exposed using a RESTful API made with Node.js. Exposed POST, GET, PATCH and DELETE HTTP methods using Express

CCC Music Emporium | ReactJS, Redux, Express, PostgreSQL, WebSocket, Mapbox, StrripAPI | Source Code

Feb 2022

- CCC Music Emporium is an online shopping website that allows users to buy or rent, also review and rating music products. The frontend is built by **React** and **TailWind** with **Redux** as state management
- The physical store locations integrated with **Mapbox**. **StripAPI** for real payment solution.
- All routes that are related with user rating and order history are verified by JsonWebToken.